The Queen's Oral Instructions
التعليمات الشفوية للملكة
Let him go
دعه يذهب
What I told Aunt Rong
ما قلته للعمة رونغ
you heard it all
لقد سمعت كل شيء
Um
واحد
Jingyuan
جينغيوان
I
أنا
Everyone in this palace wants to live
الجميع في هذا القصر يريدون العيش
It’s not easy for everyone
ليس الأمر سهلا على الجميع
But if you want to survive for yourself
ولكن إذا كنت تريد البقاء على قيد الحياة لنفسك
Then he pushed another innocent person out to die.
ثم دفع شخصًا بريئًا آخر ليموت.
So
لذا
I said
قلت
I will tell you the secret of Shufangzhai now
سأخبرك بسر شوفانغزاي الآن
Please, the queen, spare my life
من فضلك أيتها الملكة، أنقذيني
The emperor fell in love with Ziwei
لقد وقع الإمبراطور في حب زيوي
Want to make her my concubine
أريد أن أجعلها محظيتي
You should recuperate first.
ينبغي عليك التعافي أولاً.
Lin'er
لين
Ziwei was kidnapped by Grandma Rong
تم اختطاف زيوي من قبل الجدة رونغ
She said let us ask you
قالت دعنا نسألك
What happened
ماذا حدث
Princess
أميرة
This is Kunning Palace
هذا هو قصر كونينج
This is not the place for you sisters to quarrel.
هذا ليس المكان المناسب للتشاجر بينكم أيها الأخوات.
She framed Ziwei
لقد قامت بتأطير Ziwei
You still have to speak for her
لا يزال عليك أن تتحدث عنها
I didn't help her
لم اساعدها
I don't understand her either
أنا أيضا لا أفهمها
It seems that Ziwei was stabbed and the plot has been reset.
يبدو أن زيوي طُعن وتم إعادة ضبط المؤامرة.
I also want to survive
انا ايضا اريد البقاء على قيد الحياة
Don't blame me
لا تلومني
Ziwei, she did nothing wrong
زيوي، لم تفعل شيئا خاطئا
Naturally, I won’t suffer too much.
بطبيعة الحال، لن أعاني كثيرا.
What do you mean nothing will happen?
ماذا تقصد بأنه لن يحدث شيء؟
You traitor, Gege
أنت خائن، جيجي
Ziwei is so weak
زيوي ضعيف جدًا
She was locked up in Grandma Rong's little dark room
لقد تم حبسها في غرفة الجدة رونغ الصغيرة المظلمة
How can she bear it?
كيف تستطيع أن تتحمل ذلك؟
You're trying to survive for yourself
أنت تحاول البقاء على قيد الحياة لنفسك
The person who betrays his sister
الشخص الذي يخون أخته
My little swallow
سنوني الصغير
There is no friend like you
لا يوجد صديق مثلك
starting from today
ابتداء من اليوم
you are no longer my friend
أنت لم تعد صديقي
I
أنا
This slave is Kunning Palace Lin'er
هذه العبد هي لين إير من قصر كونينج
If you have something to report, please report it to your concubine
إذا كان لديك شيء لتبلغ عنه، يرجى إبلاغ خليلتك
Please help grandma to convey this
من فضلك ساعد الجدة في نقل هذا
Mammy
مامي
It's Shufangzhai Ziwei Princess who is in trouble
إنها الأميرة شوفانغزاي زيوي التي في ورطة
Ziwei Gege has always been favored by the emperor
لقد كان زيوي جيجي دائمًا مفضلًا لدى الإمبراطور
fight out
القتال
go out
الخروج
The weasel pays New Year greetings to the chicken
يهنئ ابن عرس الدجاجة بالعام الجديد
Not well-intentioned
ليس حسن النية
You have to rely on me to save Ziwei
عليك الاعتماد علي لإنقاذ زيوي
Fuku adult
فوكو بالغ
Princess Ge Ling is waiting for us.
الأميرة جي لينغ تنتظرنا.
Brother Five, please come back.
الأخ الخامس، من فضلك عد.
The emperor has rested
لقد استراح الإمبراطور
Fifth elder brother Fifth elder brother
الأخ الأكبر الخامس الأخ الأكبر الخامس
little swallow
السنونو الصغير
Why is it you?
لماذا انت؟
I
أنا
I forgot
لقد نسيت
You are the queen's lackey
أنت خادم الملكة
explain
يشرح
Where is Ziwei?
أين زيوي؟
I'm also here to save Ziwei
أنا هنا أيضًا لإنقاذ زيوي
But I didn't find it
ولكنني لم أجده
You liar
انت كاذب
I
أنا
Where are you going, little swallow?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب أيها السنونو الصغير؟
I'm going to save Ziwei
سأنقذ زيوي
I will destroy this Kunning Palace today.
سأدمر قصر كونينج هذا اليوم.
I want to rescue her too
أريد انقاذها أيضا
What are you doing to save Ziwei?
ماذا تفعل لإنقاذ زيوي؟
Rely on your three-legged cat skills
اعتمد على مهارات قطتك ذات الأرجل الثلاثة
I still rely on your arsenal
لا أزال أعتمد على ترسانتك
This is the heavily guarded Kunning Palace
هذا هو قصر كونينج الخاضع لحراسة مشددة
How I save Ziwei is my business
كيف أنقذ زيوي هو عملي
You don't need to worry about it
لا داعي للقلق بشأن ذلك
Ziwei is in danger now
زيوي في خطر الآن
This is not the time for you to lose your temper
هذا ليس الوقت المناسب لتفقد أعصابك
little swallow
السنونو الصغير
What do I want?
ماذا أريد؟
Only then can you cooperate with me
حينها فقط يمكنك التعاون معي
That's it
هذا كل شيء
I swear to you
أقسم لك
If I didn't really save Ziwei
إذا لم أنقذ زيوي حقًا
I'll be struck by lightning and die.
سوف أتعرض للضرب بالبرق وأموت.
Such a poisonous oath
مثل هذا القسم السام
I send three hundred every day
أرسل ثلاثمائة كل يوم
that's you
هذا انت
Then let me tell you a secret
إذن دعني أخبرك بسر
You will definitely believe me after hearing this
سوف تصدقني بالتأكيد بعد سماع هذا
I know
أنا أعرف
who
من
you tell me
أخبرني أنت
Where did the queen hide crape myrtle?
أين خبأت الملكة شجرة الكريب الميرتل؟
What does it have to do with you
ما علاقة هذا بك؟
go out
الخروج
Please tell me where Ziwei is
من فضلك قل لي أين زيوي
I want to save her, I told her to get out
أريد أن أنقذها، قلت لها أن تخرج
If I have the intention to harm Ziwei
إذا كان لدي نية لإيذاء زيوي
Why should I suffer these crimes?
لماذا يجب أن أعاني من هذه الجرائم؟
Just tell me where she is
فقط أخبرني أين هي
I'll prove it to you
سأثبت لك ذلك
i can't help you
لا أستطيع مساعدتك
what are you doing
ماذا تفعل
Stop pretending
توقف عن التظاهر
It's not that you can't help me
ليس الأمر أنك لا تستطيع مساعدتي
But you have to save her yourself
ولكن عليك أن تنقذها بنفسك
I know what you're thinking
أنا أعلم ما تفكر فيه
If you don't go
إذا لم تذهب
Fifth elder brother and Erkang will take action
الأخ الأكبر الخامس وإركانج سيتخذان إجراءً
At that time, the Queen asked
وفي ذلك الوقت سألت الملكة
It will only involve more people
لن يؤدي هذا إلا إلى إشراك المزيد من الناس
Even if it succeeds
حتى لو نجح
The Queen will also doubt you
والملكة سوف تشك فيك أيضًا
Because you are the only one who knows the whereabouts of Ziwei
لأنك الوحيد الذي يعرف مكان وجود زيوي
I'm responsible for the consequences
أنا المسؤول عن العواقب
Nothing to do with you
لا علاقة لك
I want it to be related to me
أريد أن يكون مرتبطا بي
Adult Kei
كي البالغ
The queen fell asleep
لقد نامت الملكة
If you have anything to do, let me know tomorrow.
إذا كان لديك أي شيء لتفعله، فأخبرني غدًا.
You think of a way to hold down Grandma Rong
أنت تفكر في طريقة للسيطرة على الجدة رونغ
Grandma Rong
الجدة رونغ
Help us buy time to save Ziwei
ساعدنا في شراء الوقت لإنقاذ زيوي
This way you won't be suspected
بهذه الطريقة لن يتم الاشتباه بك
Ziwei can also suffer less torture
يمكن لزيوي أيضًا أن يعاني من تعذيب أقل
I have something important to report to your empress
لدي شيء مهم لأبلغ به إمبراطورتك
It's about the emperor
إنه يتعلق بالإمبراطور
I'm just afraid that after tonight
أنا خائف فقط أنه بعد الليلة
It's too late
لقد فات الأوان
Whatever
أيا كان
Come with me slave
تعال معي يا عبد
Shimokonan Shimokonan
شيموكونان شيموكونان
Going to Jiangnan again
الذهاب إلى جيانغنان مرة أخرى
as an emperor
كإمبراطور
Not staying in the capital
عدم البقاء في العاصمة
Thinking about running out every day
أفكر في النفاد كل يوم
This time, he even hid it from me
هذه المرة، حتى أنه أخفى الأمر عني
Queen, calm down
يا ملكة، اهدئي
The emperor is also afraid that you will be angry
الإمبراطور أيضًا خائف من أن تغضب
I hid it from you
لقد اخفيتها عنك
Jingyuan
جينغيوان
exist
يخرج
You follow the Holy Master down to the south of the Yangtze River
تتبع المعلم المقدس إلى الجنوب من نهر اليانغتسي
Help me keep an eye on the emperor
ساعدني في مراقبة الإمبراطور
To prevent him from being confused again
لمنعه من الارتباك مرة أخرى
Get some cats, three dogs, and four dogs back.
احصل على بعض القطط، وثلاثة كلاب، وأربعة كلاب مرة أخرى.
yes
نعم
It's my turn tonight, Grandma Li, to be on duty
لقد جاء دوري الليلة، يا جدتي لي، لأكون في الخدمة
I can't let Grandma Rong be the prettiest.
لا أستطيع أن أسمح لجدتي رونغ أن تكون الأجمل.
Say it quickly
قلها بسرعة
You sneak into the palace
تتسلل إلى القصر
Whose instruction was it?
من كانت هذه التعليمات؟
What's the plan
ما هي الخطة
No one ordered me
لم يأمرني أحد
No plot
لا يوجد مؤامرة
Even if you starve me to death
حتى لو أجوعتني حتى الموت
beat me to death
ضربني حتى الموت
I have nothing to say to you either
ليس لدي ما أقوله لك أيضًا
Where does all this nonsense come from?
من أين يأتي كل هذا الهراء؟
explain
يشرح
Say it
قلها
crape myrtle
الكريب ميرتل
old witch
الساحرة العجوز
I'll let you try it too
سأدعك تجربها أيضًا
crape myrtle
الكريب ميرتل
Walk
يمشي
Let's go out first
دعنا نخرج أولا
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
It's okay Ziwei
لا بأس يا زيوي
Walk
يمشي
Lin'er Lin'er
لين'ر لين'ر
You are covered with injuries
أنت مغطى بالإصابات
I'll do it
سأفعلها
Stop talking nonsense and go
توقف عن الكلام الهراء واذهب
Walk
يمشي
Slower
أبطأ